Finding Aid for the The Sigaux Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Étranger - Heinrich Böll. Press clippings, typed newsletter (Éditions Spes). (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Wolfgang Borchert. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - J. L. Borgès (Jorge Louis Borgès). Press clippings, journal excerpts, typed transcripts (2, radio). (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - James Boswell, 1740-1795. Press clippings, typed notes, journal excerpts. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Michel Boulgakov, 1891-1940. Journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Ivan Bounine. Journal excerpts, press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Elizabeth Bowen. Press clippings, G. S. notes. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Kay Boyle. Journal excerpts. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Bradbury (Ray Bradbury). Journal excerpt, book advertisement pages. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Georg Brandès. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Kazimierz Brandys. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Joseph Breitbach. Press clippings, book advertisement page, journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Lili Brik. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Herman Broch. Journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Max Brod. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Iossip Brodski. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Louis Bromfield. Printed bibliographic notecard, journal excerpts, book catalog page, G. S. notes. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Thomas Browne. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Robert Browning. Journal excerpt, press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Constantin Brunner. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Pearl Buck. Press clippings, book advertisement pages, printed bibliographic notecards, journal excerpts, notes in a different hand. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Miodrag Bulatovik. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Edward Bulwer Lytton. Typed manuscript (photocopy with corrections: "Préface pour les Derniers Jours de Pompéi" by Claude Zaugg-Girard). (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Jacob Burckhardt, 1818-1897. Book advertisement pages, journal excerpt, G. S. notes. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Carl Burckhardt. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Anthony Burgess. Journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Edgar Rice Burroughs. Press clippings, journal excerpts. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Étranger - William Burroughs. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Samuel Butler. Journal excerpts, press clippings, book advertisement page. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Dino Buzzati. Book advertisement pages, press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Byron (George Gordon Byron, Lord). Press clippings, book excerpts (illustrations), journal excerpts, G. S. notes. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Étranger - James Cain. G. S. notes, notes in a different hand, press clippings, typed manuscript ("Préface à 'Three of a Kind'"). (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Erskine Caldwell. Journal excerpts, press clipping, notes in a different hand. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Taylor Caldwell. Journal excerpt, G. S. notes, typed manuscript ("les Oiseaux de Proie"), book advertisement pages. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Italo Calvino. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Roy Campbell, 1901-1957. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Elias Canetti. Press clippings, journal excerpts, book jacket excerpt, book advertisement page, correspondence (to G. S. from Jacques Canetti). (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Canudo. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Karel Capek. Press clippings, journal excerpts. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Truman Capote. Journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Matei Caragiale. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Vincenzo Cardarelli. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Alejo Carpentier. Biographical notecards, press clippings, journal excerpt, typed transcript (radio). (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Nick Carter. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Joyce Cary. Journal excerpts. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Hopalong Cassidy. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Carlo Cassola. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Ferreira de Castro. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Willa Cather, 1873-1947. Press clippings, journal excerpts, G. S. notes, notes in a different hand, typed transcript/newsletter (Supplement: Arts, Lettres, Education...). (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Constantin Cavafy. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Paul Celan. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Cellini (Benvenuto Cellini). Typed transcript (radio). (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Cervantès (Miguel de Cervantès Saavedra). Press clippings, book catalog pages, journal excerpts, typed transcripts (2, radio), G. S. notes. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Varlam Chalamov. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Raymond Chandler. Journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Leslie Charteris. Book advertisement page. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - J. H. Chase (James Hadley Chase). Press clippings (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Richard Chase. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Chatterton (Thomas Chatterton). Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Chaucer. Journal excerpts. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Léon Chestov. Book advertisement pages, press clippings, typed transcript (radio), journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Peter Cheyney. Press clipping, book advertisement pamphlet/booklet. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Victor Chklovski. Book advertisement pages, press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Mikhaïl Cholokhov, 1905, Prix Nobel 1965. Press clippings, book advertisement pages, journal excerpts. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Noam Chomsky. Press clippings, book advertisement page. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Kate Chopin, 1851-1904. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - John Clare. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - John Cleland. Correspondence (to G. S. from Henri Beige), typed manuscript (introduction by Henri Beige for his translation of Cleland's "Fanny Hill: Memoires d'une Fille de Joie"). (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Carlo Coccioli. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Leonard Cohen. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Coleridge (Samuel Taylor Coleridge). Press clipping, typed transcript (radio). (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - John Collier. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Richard Collier. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Wilkie Collins, 1824-1889. Press clipping, G. S. notes. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Ivy Compton-Burnett. Press clippings, journal excerpts, book advertisement page. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Cyrol Connolly. Press clipping, G. S. notes. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Henri Conscience, 1812-1883. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - James Fenimore Cooper. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Marie Corelli. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Julio Cortazar. Journal excerpt, press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Heinz von Cramer. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Stephen Crane. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Croce (Benedetto Croce). Press clippings, book catalog page, G. S. notes, journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - A. J. Cronin, 1896. G. S. notes, notes in a different hand, book advertisement page. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - E. E. Cummings (Edwards Estlin Cummings). Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - E. R. Curtius. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - J. O. Curwood. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Étranger - Maria Dabrowska, 1892-1965. Newsletter (Preuves Informations). (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Serge Dagerman. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Dante (Dante Alighieri). Journal excerpts, press clippings, typed transcripts (2, radio). (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Darwin (Charles Darwin). Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Alexandra David-Neel, 1868. Press clippings, journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Eugène Debs. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Daniel Defoë (Daniel Defoe / Daniel de Foë). Journal excerpts. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Grazia Deledda, 1875-1936. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Tibor Déry. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Edmundo Desnoes. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Issac Deutscher. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Monica Dickens. Typed biographies, G. S. notes. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Emily Dickenson. Journal excerpt, typed transcripts (2, radio and article). (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - John Dickson Carr. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Disraëli (Benjamin Disraeli). Journal excerpts, press clipping, G. S. notes. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Milovan Djilas. Journal excerpt, press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Alfred Döblin. Journal excerpts, press clippings, book advertisement page. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Heimito von Doderer. Journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Neel Doff. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - John Donne. Book/journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - J. P. Donleavy. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Ladislas Dormandi. Correspondence (from "Les amis de Ladislas Dormandi"), journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - John Dos Passos. Book advertisement pages, journal excerpts, press clippings, typed transcript (article). (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Lloyd Douglas. G. S. notes. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Norman Douglas. Journal excerpt, book advertisement page, press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Théodore Dreiser, 1871-1945. Journal excerpt, press clippings, typed newsletter (Arts et Lettres), G. S. notes, notes in a different hand, typed manuscripts (articles/essays by Wladimir Weidlé and Maurice Lauga). (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Daphné du Maurier (Daphne du Maurier). Journal excerpts, book catalog excerpt, typed biography. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Peter Dumitriu. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Will Durant. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Étranger - Hans Fallada. Press clippings, book advertisement page. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - James T. Farell, 1904-1979. Press clippings, typed newsletter excerpts, journal excerpts, G. S. notes, typed manuscript (article). (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Howard Fast, 1914-. Press clippings, book excerpt, book advertisement page. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Edna Ferber. Book dust jacket (La Ruée vers l'Ouest (Cimarron)), typed bibliography (translations), journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Lawrence Ferlinghetti. Book advertisement page, press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Guglielmo Ferrero, 1871-1942. Journal excerpts, press clippings, book advertisement page. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Lion Feuchtwanger. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Leslie Fiedler. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Henry Fielding. Journal excerpts, press clipping, book advertisement page, book excerpt (illustrated offprint/promotional excerpt with order form). (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Elysian Fields. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Ernst Fischer. Press clippings. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Ruth Fisher, 1895-1961. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Ian Fleming {James Bond}, 1908-1964. Press clippings, journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Daniel de Foë (Daniel Defoe / Daniel Defoë). Book advertisement page, press clipping, journal excerpts, typed transcript (radio), G. S. notes. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Antonio Fogazzaro, 1842-1911. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Theodore Fontane. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - C. S. Forester. Journal excerpts, G. S. notes. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - E. M. Forester (Edward Morgan Forester). Press clippings, journal excerpts, book advertisement page. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Waldo Frank. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Gustav Frenssen. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Gustav Freytag. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Bruce Jay Friedmann. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Max Frisch. Press clippings, typed book advertisement. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Robert Frost, 1874-1963. Press clipping. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Roger Fry. Journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Carlos Fuentès. Press clipping, journal excerpt. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Étranger - Carlo Gadda. Press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - J. K. Galbraith (John-Kenneth Galbraith). Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Romulo Gallegos, 1884-1969. Press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - John Galsworthy, 1867-1933. Journal excerpts, press clippings, typed transcript (article). (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Manuel Galvez, 1882-. G. S. notes. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Gandhi (Mahatma Gandhi). Press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Angel Ganivet. Journal excerpts. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Ventura Garcia Calderon. Book advertisement pages. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Erle Stanley Gardner. Journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Elizabeth Gaskell. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Stefan George. Press clipping, journal excerpts. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - C. Virgil Gheorghiu. Book advertisement pamphlet. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Allan Ginsberg. Journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Natalia Ginzberg. Journal excerpt, press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Andréa Giovene. Press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Ernst Glaeser. Press clippings, G. S. notes, notes in a different hand. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Ellen Glasgow, 1874-1945. Journal excerpt, typed manuscripts (2, G. S. article/review). (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Hubert Gold. Press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Oliver Goldsmith. Typed transcript (radio). (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Ramon Gomez de la Serna. Press clippings, book advertisement and catalog pages, journal excerpt, typed transcript (radio). (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Gongora. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Ferndinand Gonseth. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Gontcharov (Ivan Alexandrowitsch Gontscharov / Gontcharov / Gontscharow). Press clipping, typed manuscript (essay/article), book excerpt (in german, photocopy), journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Maxime Gorki. Press clippings, typed manuscript (photocopy of an article by Gabrielle Rolin), journal and book excerpts, book advertisement pages, G. S. notes, memo (to M. G. Burnand, from Yvonne Rosso, cc. to G. S.). (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - William Goyen. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Juan Goytisolo. Press clippings, journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Baltazar Gracian. Book advertisement pamphlet (with subscription form), press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Gunter Grass. Press clippings, journal excerpts. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Robert Graves. Press clippings, G. S. notes, journal excerpts, book advertisement pages. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Henry Green. Press clippings, journal excerpts. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Martin Green. Journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Gerald Green. Journal excerpt/book advertisement pages. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Grimmelshausen (Jacob Christoph von Grimmelshausen). Press clipping, journal/book excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Alexandre Grine. Typed transcript (radio). (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Giovanni Guareschi, 1908-1968. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Nicolas Guillen. Press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Joao-Guimaraes-Rosa (Joâo Guimarâes-Rosa). Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Eugénie Guinzbourg. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Georges Gurdjieff, 1877-1949 (Georges Ivanovitch Gurdjieff). Journal excerpts, press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Georges Gurvitch, 1894-1965. Journal excerpts, book advertisement pages, press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Étranger - Radclyffe Hall. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Dag Hammarsköld. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Dashiel Hammett, 1894-1961. Press clippins, journal excerpts, book advertisement pages. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Knut Hamsun. Press clippings, book advertisement page. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Frank Harris (Folder 1). Book advertisement page. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Frank Harris (Folder 2). Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Bret Harte. Journal excerpts. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Hasek (Jaroslav Hasek). Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Gerhardt Hauptmann. Press clipping, G. S. notes. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - John Hawks. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Nathaniel Hawthorne. Press clippings, journal and book excerpts, typed transcripts (2, radio), G. S. notes. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Haïm Hazaz. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Lafcadio Hearn. Journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Ben Hecht. Journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Hegel, 1770-1831 (Friedrich Hegel). Book advertisement and catalog pages, journal excerpts, press clippings, G. S. notes. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Martin Heidegger. Press clippings, journal excerpts, book advertisement pages, typed transcript (radio). (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Henri Heine. Press clippings, journal excerpt, book advertisement page. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Robert Henriques. Typed biography. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Joseph Hergesheimer. Book advertisement page. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Alexandre Herzen. Press clippings, book advertisement excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Hermann Hesse. Press clippings, journal excerpts, G. S. notes. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Étranger - Aidan Higgins. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Patricia Highsmith. Journal excerpt, press clippings, book advertisement page. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Nazim Hikmet. Press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Chester Himes. Journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Marek Hlasko. Press clipping, journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - E. T. A. Hoffmann (Ernest Théodore Amadeus Hoffmann). Press clippings, book catalog and advertisement pages. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Hölderlin (Frédéric Hölderlin). Journal excerpts, typed transcripts (4, radio), book advertisement pages, press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - G. M. Hopkins (Gerald Manley Hopkins). Press clipping, journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - A. E. Housman, 1859-1936 (Alfred Edward Housman). Journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Fereydoun Hoveyda. Newsletter (Preuves Informations). (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - W. H. Hudson. Book/journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Stephen Hudson. Book advertisement pages, journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Friedrich von Hügel. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Richard Hughes. Journal excerpt, press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Langston Hughes. Press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Fanny Hurst. Typed biography with G. S. notes. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Julian Huxley. Journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Thomas Huxley. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Étranger - Francis Iles. Book advertisement pages, journal excerpt. Internal Folder: Berkley Iles (Anthony Berkley). Journal excerpt (bibliography). (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Gyula Illyés. Press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Christopher Isherwood. Press clippings, book advertisement pages, journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Panait Istrati, 1884-1935. Press clippings, book and journal excerpts, G. S. notes. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Venceslov Ivanov, 1866-1949. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Vsevolod Ivanov. Press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Charles Jackson. Typed transcript (article). (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - W. W. Jacobs, 1863-1943. Journal excerpts, G. S. notes. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - J. P. Jacobsen (Jens-Peter Jacobsen). Journal excerpt, G. S. notes, press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Roman Jakobson. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Walter Jens. Journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Johannès Jensen. Press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Uwe Johnson. Press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Eyvind Johnson, Nobel '74 (Eyvind Olof Verner Johnson). Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - James Jones. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - C. G. Jung, 1875-1960 (Carl Gustav Jung). Book advertisement pages, press clippings, typed transcript (radio), journal excerpt, G. S. notes. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Ernst Jünger. Journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Tamizaki Junichiro. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Isabelle Kaïser. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Valentin Kataiev (Valentin Kataév). Press clipping, journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Yasunari Kawabata, 1899, Prix Nobel 1968. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Sheila Kay-Smith. Journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Iouri Kazakov. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Elia Kazan. Press clipping, journal excerpts. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Nikos Kazantzaki. Press clippings, journal excerpts, typed transcript (radio). (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Gottfried Keller. Journal excerpts. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Margaret Kennedy, 1896-1967. Book advertisement page, press clipping, notes in a different hand. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Jack Kerouac. Journal excerpts, book advertisement page, press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Gerald Kersh. G. S. notes (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Keyserling (Hermann von Keyserling). Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings. Handwritten notes. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Annette Kolb. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Hans Koningsberger. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Janus Korczak. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Jerzy Kosinski. Journal excerpts, press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Alexandre Kouprine, 1870-1938. Book advertisement page. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Anatoli Kouznetsov. Press clippings, journal excerpts. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Edouard Kouznetsov. Press clipping, journal excerpt. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Miroslav Krleza (Miroslav Karleja). Press clippings, journal excerpts. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Kubin (Alfred Kubin). Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Étranger - Herbert Marcuse. Press clippings, journal excerpts. (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Marinetti. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Luis Martin-Santos. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Étranger - H. K. Marks. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Étranger - Harry Martinson, Nobel 1974. Press clipping. (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Étranger - John Masefield. Press clippings. (Box 28, Folder 5)